A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication
1959-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Medical Letter, Inc
Rockefeller University
FA241
261.93 Cubic Feet 683 letter document boxes, 5 legal boxes, 1 half-letter box.
688 document boxes.
Biographical/Historical note
Martin A. Rizack is an editor for THE MEDICAL LETTER. THE MEDICAL LETTER on Drugs and Therapeutics is an independent, non-profit publication providing unbiased critical evaluation of Drugs in terms of their effectiveness, adverse effects and possible alternative medications.
Scope and Contents note
Published printed material supplied by non-profit publication.
Material consists of files used in preparing articles for THE MEDICAL LETTER for the years 1959 to 1977; each file consisting of drafts of the article, letters from consultants and manufacturers; and copies of published articles from the medical and scientific literature which were used in preparing the articles. Some in folders and some in envelopes.
Additional materials are available through 1985 (Boxes 398-688) which have received standard processing, and are described in an available PDF.
Arrangement note
Arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Initial Date received/inventoried: July 29, 1982. Rockefeller Archive Center receives additions to the collection periodically.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records are open for research twenty-five years after their creation. Select files restricted as noted. Use agreement is required prior to providing access. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Pharmacology; Medicine, Preventive; Medical sciences; Medical technology; Medical research; Medical education
- "Corticosteroids-Decadron And Other Adrenal Steroids" 1:1, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "Tetracyclines-Buffered Tetracyclines And Antibiotic Blood Level" 1:2. Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Meprobamate-Meprobamate" 1:3, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "Analgesics NIH 7519 - A New Analgesic Drug" 1:4, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Troleandomycin-Cyclamen And Tao" 1:5, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Iproniazid Marsilid" 1:6, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "Lipids-Dietary Aids For Reducing Blood Cholestrol" 1:8, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - Cytomel And Trionine" 1:9, Issue 3, 1959 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - The Choice And Cost Of Thyroid Preparations" 1:10, Issue 3, 1959 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "Thyroid Function Tests" 1:11, Issue 3, 1959 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- "Antihistamines-Dimetane" 1:14, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- "Tetracycline-Tetracyclines And Nystatin", 1:15, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "Zoxyzolamine", 1:16, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "Diabinese Correspondence" Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "Diabetes, Therapy-Orinase And Diabetes" 1:17, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "Erythromycin Esolate Ilosine" 1:18, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "Phenothiazines (Trimeprazine) Temaril" 1:19, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "Corticosteroids (Dexamethasone) - Follow Up Deramethasone" 1:20, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "Chloramphenicol-Chloromycetin" 1:2, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "Anileridine Leritine" 1:22, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "Ethoheptazine-Zactane And Zactirin" 1:23, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "Syrosingopine-Singoserp" 1:25, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "Senna-Senokot" 1:26, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- "Eye Disease-Opthalmic Steroid Preparations And Mixtures" 1:27, April 17, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "Phenylbutazone-Butazolidin And Sterazolidin" 1:30, Issue 8, 1959 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Amphotericin B-Fungizone" 1:32, Issue 8, 1959 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- "Streptococcal Infections-Drug Cost In Control Of Streptococcus Infections" 1:34, Issue 9, 1959 May 15 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- "Nitrofurantoin-Furadantin" 1:37, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- "Fuzazolidone-Furoxone" 1:38, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
- "Dextropropoxyphene-Darvon" 1:40, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- "Syrosingopine-Notes On Singoserp" 1:40, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- "Antimicrobials-Spontin And Vancocini" 1:41. Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- "Poison Ivy-Prophylaxis Of Poison Ivy Dermatitis" 1:42, Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "Syrosingopine-More On Singoserp" 1:44, Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- "Nutrition And Diet-Sustagen" 1:47. Issue 12, 1959 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- "Antihistamines-Non-Prescription Sleep Aids", 1:48, Issue 12, 1959 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- "Psoralens-Methoxysalen For Vitiligo And Suntanning" 1:49, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- "Penicillin-Penicillin V Versus Penicillin G, 1:50, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "Griseofulvin" 1:51, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- "Psoriasis-Alphosyl" 1:51, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- "Nutrition And Diet (Sustagen) - Sustagen A Correction" 1:52, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- "Mecamylamine-Inversine" 1:53, Issue 14, 1959 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- "Heparin-Clarin" 1:54, Issue 14, 1959 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
- "Iron-Oral Iron Preparations", 1:55, Issue 14, 1959 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
- "Phenothiazines-Prochlorperazine Compazine" 1:57, Issue 15, 1959 August 7 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
- "Newborn-Drug Hazards In The Newborn" 1:58, Issue 15, 1959 August 7 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- "Parkinson's Disease-Antiparkinsonism Drug", 1:59, Issue 15, 1959 August 7 (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
- "Griseofulvin" 1:61, Issue 16, 1959 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- "Bretylium Tosylate-A New Antihypersensitive Drug" 1:64, Issue 16, 1959 August 12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- "Imipramine-Tofranil" 1:65, Issue 17, 1959 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- "Vitamins-B12" 1:67, Issue 17, 1959 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- "Anergex" 1:68, Issue 17, 1959 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- "Rauwolfias-Rauwolfias Products In Hypertension" 1:70, Issue 18, 1959 September 18 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Enzyme Tests For Urine Sugar" 1:72, Issue 18, 1959 September 18 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- "Sulfonamides-Long Acting Sulfonamides" 1:73, Issue 19, 1959 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
- "Furaltadone-Altafur" 1:75, Issue 19, 1959 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- "Skin Disease Therapy-Acid Mantle Creme" 1:76, Issue 19, 1959 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- "Depression Therapy-A Note On Drug Therapy Of Depression" 1:77, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- "Isocarboxazid-Marplan" 1:78, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
- "Costicosteroids-Note On Adrenal Steroids" 1:80, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- "Antihistamines-Polaramine And Disomer" 1:83, Issue 21, 1959 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
- "Antimicrobials-Dihydrostrptomycin And Kanamycin" 1:83, Issue 21, 1959 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- "Anticoagulants-Oral Anticoagulant Drugs" 1:85, Issue 22, 1959 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 8-11)
- "Penicillin Allergy-Penicillin" 1:87, Issue 22, 1959 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
- "Respiratory Disease (Vaccines) - Vaccines For Respiratory Virus Infection" 1:88, Issue 22, 1959 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- "Tetracyclines-Declomycin" 1:89, Issue 23, 1959 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- "Hypertension-Pitfalls In Some Life Insurance Statistics" 1:90, Issue 23, 1959 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- "Meprobate Prepns-Deprol" 1:92, Issue 23, 1959 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- "Fibrinolytic Agents-Actase And Streptokinase", 1:93, Issue 24, 1959 December 11 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Topical Corticosteroids" 1:94, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- "Corticosteroids, Tropical-Tropical Corticosteroids" 1:94, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- "Immunization (Vaccines) Quadrigan And Tetravex" 1:96, Issue 24, 1959 December 11 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "Penicillins-Syncillin", 1:97, Issue 25, 1959 December 25 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- "Liver Diseases-Infections Hepatitis And Immune Globulin" 1:98, Issue 25, 1959 December 25 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- "Epilepsy-Anti-Epilepsy Drug" 1:99, Issue 25, 1959 December 25 (Box 7, Folder 12-14)
- "Smoking-Smoking And Lung Cancer" 2:1, Issue 26, 1960 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- "Iron, Injectable-Imferon" 2:2, Issue 26, 1960 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
- "Parasitic Infections-Povan And Other Anthelmintic Drugs" 2:4, Issue 26, 1960 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "Chloroquines-Manuscript Aralen And Plaquenil" 2:5, Issue 27, 1960 January 22 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
- "Progestational Hormones-Enovid, Norlutin, and Delalutin" 2:7, Issue 27, 1960 January 22 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
- "Hydroxyzine-Atarax And Vistril" 2:9, Issue 28, 1960 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
- "Obesity-Appetite Depressants" 2:11, Issue 28, 1960 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Topical Corticosteroids - A Correction", 2:12, Issue 28, 1960 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- "Trimethidinium Methosulfate Otensin - A New Antihypertensive" 2:13, Issue 29, 1960 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
- "Tetracyclines, Syntetrin - A New Parenteral Tetracycline" 2:14, Issue 29, 1960 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- "Angina Pectoris-Organic Nitrates For The Control Of Angina Pectoris" 2:17, Issue 30, 1960 March 14 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
- "Flavonoids-CVP" 2:19, Issue 30, 1960 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- "Parasitic Infections-Pinworms" 2:20, Issue 30, 1960 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- "Cyclophosphamide-Cytoxan" 2:21, Issue 31, 1960 March 18 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
- "Shock Therapy-Vasopressor Drugs For Shock" 2:22, Issue 31, 1960 March 18 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
- "Salicylates-Arthropan" 2:23, Issue 31, 1960 March 18 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
- "Estrogen-Premarin for Bleeding" 2:28, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- "Shock Therapy-Levophed and Aramine" 2:29, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- "Estrogen-Premarin for Bleeding" 2:28, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- "Shock Therapy-Levophed and Aramine" 2:29, Issue 33, 1960 April 15 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
- "Phemetrazine-Preludin" 2:31, Issue 33, 1960 April 15 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
- "Vitamins-Homagenets and Vitamin Absorption" 2:32, Issue 33, 1960 April 15 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
- "Methyprylon-Noludar, A "Non-Barbiturate" Hypnotic" 2:35, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
- "Halothane-Fluothane" 2:36, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- "Polyurethane Foam-Ostamer" 2:36, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- "Chlordiazepoxide-Librium" 2:37, Issue 35, 1960 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
- "Diarrhea-Traveler's Diarrhea" 2:38, Issue 35, 1960 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- "Iron, Injectable-Imteron" 2:40, Issue 35, 1960 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- "Estrogens-Estrogens for Menopausal Symptoms" 2:41, Issue 36, 1960 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
- "Analgesics (Antipyretic) Pabalate" 2:43, Issue 36, 1960 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- "Contraceptives-The Birth Control Pill" 2:45, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- "Progestational Hormones-Provera" 2:46, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- "Antimicrobials-Hot Weather Stability of Antibotics" 2:48, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- "Shock Therapy-Five Vasporessors" 2:50, Issue 38, 1960 June 24 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- "Nutrition & Diet-Metrecal" 2:51, Issue 38, 1960 June 24 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- "Ergotamine Prepns-New and Old Ergotamine Drugs for Migraine" 2:54, Issue 39, 1960 July 8 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
- "Corticotropin-ACTH Versus Corticosteroids" 2:55, Issue 39, 1960 July 8 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- "Anisindione-Miradon, A New Anticoagulant" 2:58, Issue 40, 1960 July 22 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- "Nitrofurans-Reappraisal of Three Oval Nitrofurans" 2:62, Issue 41, 1960 August 5 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
- "Skin Disease (Diaper Rash) Prevention of Diaper Rash" 2:64, Issue 41, 1960 August 5 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- "Corticosteroids (Prednisone) - Tests of Prednisone" 2:65, Issue 42, 1960 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
- "Hypnotics & Sedatives-Dorraison, Placidyl, and Valmid" 2:67, Issue 42, 1960 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
- "Furaltadine-Further Note on Altafur" 2:68, Issue 42, 1960 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- "Guadethidine-Ismelin" 2:69, Issue 43, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
- "Polio Vaccines-Oral Polio Vaccines" 2:71, Issue 43, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- "Polio Vaccines-Purivax" 2:72; Issue 43, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- "Urinanalysis-Ketostix and Actest Tablets" 2:72, Issue 45, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- "Penicillins-Phenthicillin" 2:73, Issue 44, 1960 September 16 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- "Penicillins, New (Methicillin) - A New Penicillin for Resistant Staphylococci" 2:75, Issue 44, 1960 September 16 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
- "Phenothiazines (Fluphenazine) - Prolixln and Permitil" 2:77, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
- "Anticoagulants-Anticoagulant Drugs and Surgery" 2:78, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- "Urinanalysis-Albustix" 2:79, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- "Triparanol-Mer/29" 2:81, Issue 46, 1960 October 14 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- "Skin Disease, Therapy-Acne Cleansers" 2:83, Issue 46, 1960 October 14 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "Oxymorphone-Numorphan" 2:85, Issue 47, 1960 October 28 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Diloderm" 2:86, Issue 47, 1960 October 28 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- "Meprobamate" 2:87, Issue 47, 1960 October 28 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
- "Respiratory Disease (Vaccines) - Resprogen and Influenza Vaccines" 2:89, Issue 48, 1960 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- "Thyroid Disease (Hyperthyroidism) - Drug Treatment of Hyperthyroidism" 2:90, Issue 48, 1960 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
- "Vitamins, Niacin-Nicalex" 2:91, Issue 48, 1960 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- "Methenamine-Mandelamine, and Urinary Tract Infections" 2:93, Issue 49, 1960 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
- "Antacids-Antacids in Ulcer Therapy" 2:94, Issue 49, 1960 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
- "Nasal Decongestants-Otrivin" 2:96, Issue 49, 1960 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- "Phenazocine-Prinadol" 2:97, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- "Vitamins-Multi Vitamin Supplements" 2:98, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- "Corticosteroids, Side Effects-Corticosteriod Therapy in Children" 2:99, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
- "Meprobamate-Mephobamate Toxicity" 2:100, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- "Oxethazine-Oxaine" 2:103, Issue 51, 1960 December 23 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- "Chloral Hydrate" 2:104, Issue 51, 1960 December 23 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- "Chloramphenicol-Chloromycetin and Aplastic Anemia" 3:1, Issue 52, 1961 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- "Antimicrobials, Prophylactic Use (Respiratory Disease) - Antibiotic Prophylaxis of Chronic Bronchitis" 3:2, Issue 52, 1961 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- "Amphemdone-Dornwal" 3:4, Issue 52, 1961 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
- "Barbiturates-Tests of Secobarbiatal" 3:5, Issue 53, 1961 January 20 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
- "Lipoproein-Nucleic Acid Complex Reticulose" 3:7, Issue 53, 1961 January 20 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- "Trimethobenzamide-Trigan" 3:8, Issue 53, 1961 January 20 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
- "Depression Theory-Drugs for Mental Depression" 3:9, Issue 54, 1961 February 3 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- "Gout-Benemid, Auturane, and Flexin" 3:11, Issue 54, 1961 February 3 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
- "Gout-Colchicine Dosage-A Correction" 3:36, Issue 54, 1961 April 28 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- "Antimicrobials-Pencillin-Streptomycim Combinations" 3:13, Issue 55, 1961 February 17 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
- "Polio Vaccines-Poliovirus Vaccines" 3:16, Issue 55, 1961 February 17 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- "Ergotamine Prepns-Bellergal" 3:18, Issue 56, 1961 March 3 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
- "Immune Globulin-Gamma Globulin" 3:19, Issue 56, 1961 March 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- "Phenacetin-Anacin and Other Combination Drugs" 3:6, Issue 57, 1961 March 17 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
- "Fibrinolytic Agents-Thrombolysin" 3:23, Issue 57, 1961 March 17 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- "Estrogens-Premarin and Coronary Artery Disease" 3:23, Issue 57, 1961 March 17 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
- "Deanol-Deaner" 3:25, Issue 58, 1961 March 31 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
- "Hermostatics-Surgical, Oxycel, and Gelfoam" 3:26, Issue 58, 1961 March 31 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- "Piminodine-Alvodine" 3:27, Issue 58, 1961 March 31 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
- "Penicillins-Tests of Penicillin G Tablets" 3:29, Issue 59, 1961 April 14 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- "Vitamins B (Pantothenic Acid) Ilopan, Cozyme and Motilyn" 3:31, Issue 59, 1961 April 14 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
- "Oxytocin-Syntocinon" 3:32, Issue 59, 1961 April 14 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- "Antimicrobials-Cosa-Terrastatin, Mysteclin F and Declostatin" 3:33, Issue 60, 1961 April 28 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- "Prothipendyl HCl-Timovan" 3:35, Issue 60, 1961 April 28 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- "Phenylbutazone-Tandearil and Butazolidin" 3:31, Issue 61, 1961 May 12 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- "Vitamins-Fortespan and Other Sustained-Release Vitamins Products", 1961 May 12; 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- "Vitamins-Fortespan and Other Sustained-Release Vitamins Products", 1961 May 16; 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- "Bishudroxycoumarino - Tests of Dicumarol" 3:40, Issue 61, 1961 May 12 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- "Anabolic Agents-The Antabolic-Androgenic Steroids" 3:41, Issue 62, 1961 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
- "Carbazochrome-Adrenosem Salicylate and Hemostasis" 3:43, Issue 62, 1961 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
- "Sulfonamides-Sulfunamide Mixtures and Combinations" 3:45, Issue 63, 1961 June 9 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- "Motion Sickness-Motion Sickness Drugs" 3:49, Issue 64, 1961 June 23 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- "Antiemetics-Antiemetics and Postoperative Nasuea" 3:50, Issue 64, 1961 June 23 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- "Pregnancy Tests-Pro Duosterone and Early Diagnosis of Pregnancy" 3:51, Issue 64, 1961 June 23 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
- "Quinidine-Quinaglute, Cardioquin, and Quinidine Sulfate" 3:53, Issue 65, 1961 July 7 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
- "Photosensitivity-Photosensitivity Reaction to Drugs" 3:56, Issue 65, 1961 July 7 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- "Colistin-Colymyein" 3:57, Issue 66, 1961 July 21 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
- "Corticosteroids-Haldrone and Celestone" 3:58, Issue 66, 1961 July 21 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- "Antiseptics-Micrin and Oral Antibacterial Agents" 3:60, Issue 66, 1961 July 21 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- "Diarrhea-Lomotil" 3:61, Issue 67, 1961 August 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- "Glucagon" 3:62, Issue 67, 1961 August 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- "Anesthetics-Local Anesthetics" 3:62, Issue 67, 1961 August 4 (Box 26, Folder 3-6)
- "Fungal Infection-Topical Antifungal Drugs" 3:65, Issue 68, 1961 August 18 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- "Diarrhea-Soroquel" 3:66, Issue 68, 1961 August 18 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
- "Vitamin K-Vitamin K Products in the Control of Hemorrhage" 3:57, Issue 68, 1961 August 18 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- "Diabetes Therapy-Orinase, Diabinese and DBI" 3:69, Issue 69, 1961 September 1 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
- "Phenlyketonuria-Phenistix and Phenylketinuria" 3:71, Issue 69, 1961 September 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- "Dextroamphetamine-Tests of Dextroamphetamine" 3:73, Issue 70, 1961 September 15 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- "Meprobamate Prepons-Deprol" 3:75, Issue 70, 1961 September 15 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- "Parasite Infections-Delvex" 3:76, Issue 70, 1961 September 15 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- "Cancer-Chemotherapeutic Agents for Cancer" 3:77, Issue 71, 1961 September 29 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
- "Antiseptics-Dial Soap and Staphylococcal Infection" 3:79, Issue 71, 1961 September 29 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- "Skin Disease-Topical Agents for Bacterial Skin Infections" 3:81, Issue 72, 1961 October 13 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
- "Amitriptyline-Elavil" 3:83, Issue 72, 1961 October 13 (Box 29, Folder 3-5)
- "Nutrition & Diet (Nutrament) Nutrament" 3:84, Issue 72, 1961 October 13 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- "Lipids-Margarine and Coronary Artery Disease" 3:85, Issue 73, 1961 October 27 (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
- "Zoxyzolamine-Flexin" 3:86, Flexin, Issue 73, 1961 October 27 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- "Tetracyclines - The Tetracycline Antibiotics" 3:87, Issue 73, 1961 October 27 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- "Muscle Relaxants-Muscle Relaxants I" 3:89, Issue 74, 1961 November 10 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
- "Bisacodyl-Dulcolax" 3:90, Issue 74, 1961 November 10 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
- "Mebutamate Capla" 3:90, Issue 75, 1961 November 24 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- "Muscle Relaxant-Muscle Relaxants II" 3:94, Issue 75, 1961 November 24 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- "Hypertension-Drug Treatment of Hypertension" 3:97, Issue 76, 1961 December 8 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- "Systemic Fluoride for Prevention of Dental Caries" 3:100, Issue 76, 1961 December 8; 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- "Systemic Fluoride for Prevention of Dental Caries (Sources, Reprints)" 3:100, Issue 76, 1961 December 8; 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- "Thiethylperazine-Torecan" 3:104, Issue 77, 1961 December 22 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- "Cancer-New Drugs Techniques for Cancer II" 3:102, Issue 77, 1961 December 22 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
- "Chlordiazepoxide-Librium in Alcoholism" 3:101, Issue 77, 1961 December 22 (Box 31, Folder 7-9)
- "Potassium Aspartate with Magnesium Aspartate-Spartase" 4:1, Issue 78, 1962 January 5 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- "Potassium Aspartate with Magnesium Aspartate-Spartase" 4:1, Issue 78, 1962 January 5; 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- "Monoamine Oxidase Inhibitors-Mao Inhibitor in Agina Pectoris and Primary Hypertension" 4:2, Issue 78, 1962 January 5 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- "Phenothiazines (Trifluoperazine) - Stelazine" 4:38, Issue 78, 1962 May 11 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
- "Nutrition and Diet, Infants-Infant Milk Preparations" 4:7, Issue 79, 1962 January 19 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
- "Thyroid Function Test-Thyro PBI Kits" 4:8, Issue 79, 1962 January 19 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- "Antiseptics-Antiseptics for Prevention of Skin and Wound Infections" 4:9, Issue 80, 1962 February 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- "Hypertension Ganglion-Blocking Drugs in the Treatment of Hypertensive Disease" 4:10, Issue 80, 1962 February 2 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
- "Meperidine-Morphane and Demerol" 4:13, Issue 81, 1962 February 16 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
- "Cold "Remedies"-Hycomine Compound and Contac" 4:14, Issue 81, 1962 February 16 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- "Barbiturates-Plexonal, Lotusate, Tuinal, & Other Barbiturates" 4:17, Issue 82, 1962 March 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- "Hypertension-Sympatholtic Drugs for Severe Hypertension Disease" 4:18, Issue 82, 1962 March 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- "Cortico Steroids (Fluprednisolone) - Alphadrol" 4:20, Issue 82, 1962 March 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- "Cortico Steroids, Topical-Synalar, Cordran, & Other Topical Steroids" 4:21, Issue 83, 1962 March 16 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
- "Iron, Injectable-Iferon" 4:23, Issue 83, 1962 March 16 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- "Obesity-Calories Do Not Count" 4:21, Issue 83, 1962 March 16 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- "Erythromycin and Oleandomycins" 4:25, Issue 84, 1962 March 30 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- "Tranylcypromine-Parnate" 4:26, Issue 84, 1962 March 30 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
- "Colitis-Chronic Ulcerative Colitis" 4:27, Issue 84, 1962 March 30 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
- "Penicillins, New (Oxacillin) - Oxacillin 4:29, Issue 85, 1962 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
- "Colitis-Azulfidine in Ulcerative Colitis" 4:32, Issue 85, 1962 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
- "Hypertension-Anti-Hypertensive Drugs IV: The Thiazides" 4:34, Issue 86, 1962 April 27 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
- "Phenylotoloxamine Prepons-Defencin" 4:36, Issue 86, 1962 April 27 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- "Glaucoma: Effects of Systematic Anticholinergic and Other Drugs on Glaucoma" 4:37, Issue 87, 1962 May 11 (Box 36, Folder 4-6)